[{"answer": "My faith.", "docId": "121210pmt", "aSentId": 49, "question": "How are you bearing up with this?", "qSentId": 48}, {"answer": "The police officer was trying to locate me for four hours and finally got my telephone number from someone and called me while I was at work, which he didn't know I was at work.", "docId": "121210pmt", "aSentId": 52, "question": "How did you hear the news?", "qSentId": 51}, {"answer": "Well, I was upset, but I realized, you know, our youth today are young and stupid, and we was all once that age and we'd done things that we are not proud of.", "docId": "121210pmt", "aSentId": 59, "question": "How did you feel?", "qSentId": 58}, {"answer": "We can say yes and then also I think -- I think it's the individual.", "docId": "121210pmt", "aSentId": 93, "question": "That the behavior of the players off the pitch, perhaps, needs more concern?", "qSentId": 92}, {"answer": "Well, I would like Jerry to be remembered as his faith in God and being the best of friends and just an all-out scholar.", "docId": "121210pmt", "aSentId": 103, "question": "How would you like him as his mother to be remembered?", "qSentId": 102}, {"answer": "I don't know if it approaches crisis, perhaps it does but it's at a crossroads because there's an issue about the fundamental nature of the game.", "docId": "121210pmt", "aSentId": 138, "question": "A crisis, would you say?", "qSentId": 137}, {"answer": "I'm not sure what can be done about it exactly.", "docId": "121210pmt", "aSentId": 153, "question": "What can you really do about it?", "qSentId": 152}, {"answer": "I couldn't agree more.", "docId": "121210pmt", "aSentId": 175, "question": "I'm not commenting on the exact whys and where fors that will play out in the court of law about what happened between him and Trayvon Martin, but what does common sense tell you about the likelihood of that confrontation ever taking place in the first place if George Zimmerman was not carrying a gun?", "qSentId": 174}, {"answer": "Again, I'm not positioning myself as an expert, but as a private citizen, I would like to see him do that, yes.", "docId": "121210pmt", "aSentId": 287, "question": "Is it time for him to show some proper moral leadership here, do you think, and actually do something or try and do something?", "qSentId": 286}, {"answer": "Well, the reason that, as I said at the convention, I didn't leave the Republican party.", "docId": "121210pmt", "aSentId": 316, "question": "Tell me about your journey and why you have ended up now in President Obama's camp?", "qSentId": 315}, {"answer": "They're happy about it.", "docId": "121210pmt", "aSentId": 324, "question": "What do you parents make of your defection?", "qSentId": 323}, {"answer": "She would be extremely formidable.", "docId": "121210pmt", "aSentId": 341, "question": "Would you agree with that?", "qSentId": 340}, {"answer": "Well, you couldn't have said it better.", "docId": "121210pmt", "aSentId": 351, "question": "And what needs to be done to get a deal, do you think?", "qSentId": 350}, {"answer": "I would be the first one out there leading the people of this country against a tyrannical government.", "docId": "121210pmt", "aSentId": 389, "question": "Do you actually that you're all going to rise up one day against a tyrannical presidency in your own country?", "qSentId": 388}, {"answer": "Well, I guess I approach this on two levels.", "docId": "121210pmt", "aSentId": 397, "question": "James Fallows, what is your view of that?", "qSentId": 396}, {"answer": "I agree.", "docId": "121210pmt", "aSentId": 466, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 465}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, we don't know how the SEAL was killed.", "docId": "121210pmt", "aSentId": 491, "question": "And what does it tell you about the ongoing conflict in Afghanistan?", "qSentId": 490}, {"answer": "I think it will be -- actually, it will be interestingly and maybe more positively paired with the war in Iraq, the war in Iraq being an entirely discretionary war that the U.S. undertook on the basis of incorrect information.", "docId": "121210pmt", "aSentId": 511, "question": "Historically when we look back on this period, notwithstanding the death of bin Laden, do you think that the conflict in Afghanistan will be seen as anything but a rather miserable failure in the end?", "qSentId": 510}, {"answer": "I think that they do.", "docId": "121210pmt", "aSentId": 523, "question": "Do you think the politicians understand the kind of seriousness of the game that they're playing at the moment?", "qSentId": 522}, {"answer": "Let's go prop on you.", "docId": "121210pmt", "aSentId": 536, "question": "And how will it play out?", "qSentId": 535}, {"answer": "That's tough.", "docId": "121210pmt", "aSentId": 547, "question": "Who's going to be top dog in the end, do you think?", "qSentId": 546}]